Don't wait for tomorrow to live for today.
Clouds is a music, drama, romance film directed by Justin Baldoni.
Young musician Zach Sobiech discovers his cancer has
spread, leaving him just a few months to live.
With limited time, he follows his dream and makes an album,
unaware that it will soon be a viral music phenomenon.
Zach Sobiech, played by Fin Argus.
Sammy, played by Sabrina Carpenter.
Amy, played by Madison Iseman.
Laura Sobiech, played by Neve Campbell.
Rob Sobiech, played by Tom Everett Scott.
Mr. Weaver, played by Lil Rel Howery.
Clouds is a 2020 American biographical romantic musical drama teen film directed and produced by Justin
Baldoni and written by Kara Holden from a story by Holden, Patrick Kopka, and Casey La Scala.
It is based upon the memoir Fly a Little Higher: How God Answered a
Mom's Small Prayer in a Big Way by Laura Sobiech.
The film stars Fin Argus, Sabrina Carpenter, Madison Iseman, Neve Campbell, Tom Everett Scott, and Lil Rel Howery, and tells the story of Zach Sobiech,
a teenager from Minnesota who has osteosarcoma, and decides to follow his dream of becoming a musician after finding out he is dying.
Originally scheduled to be theatrically released by Warner Bros.
Pictures before the COVID-19 pandemic shut down public movie theaters, Walt Disney Studios took over the
distribution rights and released the film on their Disney+ streaming service on October 16, 2020.
The film was removed from Disney+ on May 26, 2023.
The film explores themes of life and death, based on true
story, terminal illness, cancer, aspiring musician.
The tone is emotional.